gofmx.com 2018-08-26

# Website Privacy Policy

Website Privacy Policy
In this Website Privacy Statement ("statement"), we, Facilities Management eXpress, LLC. (FMX),
provide information about how we collect, use and transfer personally identifiable data from you,
an individual person and website visitor, through FMX’s publicly accessible websites (any of our
websites such as https://www.gofmx.com/ that can be accessed without a password) and on which
we post a direct link to this statement (collectively the "site"). This statement is designed to
address various laws and regulations such as the GDPR.
Scope
This statement covers only data collected through the site and not any other data collection or
processing, including, without limitation, data collection practices of webpages to which the site
links, or data that we or our affiliates collect offline or through webpages that do not display a
direct link to this statement.
Types of Data and Collection Methods
Through the site, we receive data that you actively submit as well as data that we track:
Actively Submitted Data: When you request information, subscribe to a mailing list or for a service,
respond to an online survey or otherwise actively send us data, we usually collect data such as your
name, e-mail address(es), mailing address(es), telephone number(s), and certain information
related to the business you represent such as number of employees and industry type. You can opt
out of providing information by not entering it when asked and, if such information is required in
order to allow us to respond to your inquiry, you will receive a notice advising you of this. In each
such instance, you will know what data we collect through the site, because you actively submit it.
Passively Tracked Data: When you visit the site, we also passively track information on your
computer and Internet connection, such as the IP address of your computer and/or Internet service
provider, the date and time you access the site, the Internet address of websites from which you
link to our site, the computer technology you are using and your movements and preferences on
our site. We use technology that many other websites employ, including, without limitation,
"cookies" or small data files stored on your computer's hard drive, to collect such information. In
some instances, we also use cookies to collect information in connection with future visits from that
website, to recognize you as a previous visitor, or to track your activity on our site. If you follow a
link to the site from an affiliate or promotion, we store information about your arrival from that
                                                  FMX-PP. Ver2.0

affiliate or promotion in a session cookie. You do not need to have cookies turned on to visit our
site. You can refuse cookies by turning them off on your browser. But, if you want to access
webpages that require registration, you need to accept a mandatory session cookie, which you can
delete after you leave the site.
Combinations: Unless you also actively submit personal information such as your name or address,
passively tracked data does not typically allow us to identify you personally (even though it can
theoretically be done, we do not have the means or an interest to find out who you are, unless you
identify yourself voluntarily through an active submission of data). To the extent permitted by
applicable law, we reserve the right to combine passively tracked data with personal data that you
actively submit.
Collection Purposes, Use of Data
We collect passively tracked data primarily for purposes of administering, protecting and improving
our site and our systems, to better understand the preferences of our site visitors, to identify server
problems, to compile aggregated statistics about site usage, and to help personalize your
experience on our site. We do not deliver third party online advertisements on our sites but we
advertise our products and services on others' Web sites. We work with service providers to deliver
retargeting advertisements and other advertisements on our behalf to visitors of our
www.gofmx.com site.
We collect actively submitted data primarily for two purposes: Firstly, for the purpose for which you
originally sent us the data (e.g., to provide information to you or sign you up for a free trial); and
secondly, for purposes of contacting you to further discuss your interest in our company, the
services we provide and ways we can improve them to provide information on services, promotions
and events. You can opt out of receiving marketing emails as explained below.
Disclosures of Personal Information
We are not in the business of selling or renting your information to telemarketers and we do not
share your personally identifiable information with others, except as follows: We freely share your
information with FMX employees. We also may share information with trusted business partners,
such as system integrators, distributors, and referral partners and any other party specifically
identified on the page on which you submit your information. We may share your information as
required by law or in the interest of protecting or exercising our or others' legal rights, e.g., without
limitation, in connection with requests from law enforcement officials and in connection with court
proceedings. We may share or transfer your information in connection with a prospective or actual
sale, merger, transfer or other reorganization of all or parts of our business. Also, we reserve the
right to fully use and disclose any information that is not in personally identifiable form (such as
statistics and survey results that do not identify you individually by name).
                                                  FMX-PP. Ver2.0

Opt-Out
In connection with promotions or other projects, we may ask you specifically whether you have
objections against a certain kind of data use or sharing. If you opt-out under such circumstances, we
will respect your decision. To opt out of receiving commercial communications from FMX, please
click on the "unsubscribe" link in the communication or, please contact us at support@gofmx.com.
Please note that our affiliates and other data recipients have their own data privacy policies, which
may differ from ours and you would have to contact them separately with respect to opt-out
requests.
Access
If personal information you have submitted through the site is no longer accurate, current, or
complete, and you wish to update it, please send an e-mail to support@gofmx.com. Upon
appropriate request we will usually be glad to update or amend your information, but we reserve
the right to use information obtained previously to verify your identity or take other actions that we
believe are appropriate.
Security
Transmissions over the Internet are never 100% secure or error-free. However, we take reasonable
steps to protect your personal information from loss, misuse, and unauthorized access, disclosure,
alteration, and destruction.
Effective Date, Amendments
This statement is effective as of May 21, 2018. We reserve the right to change, modify, add or
remove portions of this statement from time to time and in our sole discretion, but will alert you
that changes have been made by indicating on the statement the date it was last updated. When
you visit the site, you are accepting the current version of this statement as posted on the site at
that time. We recommend that users revisit this statement on occasion to learn of any changes.
Contact Us
Please feel free to contact us with any comments, questions, complaints or suggestions you might
have regarding the information practices described in this statement. You may send us an e-mail at
support@gofmx.com or write to us Facilities Management eXpress, LLC. 800 Yard St., Suite 115,
Columbus, OH 43212, telephone: 1 (844) 664-4400.
                                                FMX-PP. Ver2.0
